Ahmed Siddique

03495486080 Ch379796@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed-siddique-

2a1918247/

Over the past three years of my Computer Science degree at Air University, I've undertaken a diverse range of coding projects to enhance my skills. Notable projects include a Flight Reservation System incorporating OOP concepts, a Library Management System developed with Django, and a multithreaded Ludo game in C++. I've also explored web development by cloning GitHub Pages, creating a Todo list and calculator using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Progressing to React, I implemented a Todo list, cart system, and Tic Tac Toe game. Each project has contributed to my understanding of various programming paradigms and technologies, marking my continuous journey of learning and practical application.

Experience

SEPTEMBER 2022 - OCTOBER 2022

Let's GROW MORE/ Flutter Developer

I Completed my 1-month Internship in Mobile Application Developer in LET'S GROW More. I have a wonderful experience to be work as a flutter developer in the group.

JUNE 2022 - AUGUST 2022

PSEB IT Industry Academia Bridge Program 2022

I enjoy a wonderful experience of Academia bridge program in Mobile App Development Flutter.

JANUARY 2023 - FEBRUARY 2022

AUCIS Web Development Boot camp 2023

After a semester I avail my free time to enhance my skill by taking AUCIS web development boot camp.

Certifications

JANUARY 2023 - FEBRUARY 2022

AUCIS Web Development Boot camp 2023

After a semester I avail my free time to enhance my skill by taking AUCIS web development boot camp.

Python Django – The Practical Guide Udemy

I enhanced my backend development skills by learning python Django Framework.

React - The Complete Guide 2023 Udemy

In the journey of learning react I lean many things like props ,state ,lifting-up-state, react router, react query and many more concepts.

Projects

React Landing page of ecommerce application

I create a landing page of ecommerce application which is developed by React and CSS.

https://glittery-meringue-27a5b8.netlify.app/

LUDO With C++ and Multithreading:

In me semester project of Operating System I developed Ludo with C++ and Semaphores.

Flight Reservation C++ and OOP:

Develop C++ Flight Reservation Project in my second semester project

Skills

• CSS HTML JavaScript • Django • Flutter • Dart • Machine Learning • React • Nodejs • Next JS

Education

SEPTEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

Bachelor in Computer Science /Air University, Islamabad,